[intro to "Let Me Entertain You" by Robbie Williams]
[Robbie Williams VO] Good evening, folks, hmm...
Good evening, you slags.
No, good evening, folks.
So, who is Robbie Williams?
Well, I've been called many things -
narcissistic, punchable,shit-eating twat,
but while I'm all those things,
I wanna show you
how I really see myself.
So sit back, relax,
while I give you a right
fucking entertaining.
So, the story starts...
[Robbie VO]
1982, Stoke-on-Trent.
The arse-end of the
north of England.
[boy 1] Mitchell.
It may look grubby
and deprived...
- [boy 2] Troy.
- But deep down...
- [boy 1] Wayne.
- it was grubby and deprived.
[boy 2] Mason.
I didn't have much,
but at least
I had the respect...
- [boy 1] Crystal.
- and admiration of my peers.
[Robbie] What?!
[Robbie VO] They just had
trouble showing it.
- [boy 2] Robert.
- Yes! Come on! [Grunts]
Oi! Right, knobhead,
pass the ball to Nate
and let him do the rest.
Positions!
Oi! The fuck you off to?
You're in goal.
- But...
- Don't fuck it up.
I'm like a chainmail condom,
nothing's getting through.
Whoo! Let's go, slags!
[Robbie VO]
I had plenty of balls.
But I couldn't stop
a single one.
I wasn't ready. Ohh!
- [boy] Nice one, dickhead.
- Come on!
[Robbie screaming] Oh!
Robert Williams,
captain of Port Vale.
[children roaring]
[thudding] [children laughing]
[boy] You really are fucking
useless, aren't ya?
[children laughing]
[girl] Little bitch!
It's alright, Rob.
Nate, just leave it.
Yeah... Yeah, jog on, you tit.
- [children laughing]
- Right, come on, let's go.
You're a fucking nobody!
[sniffles]
[Robbie VO]
See, where I grew up,